mygreatlakes.org 2019-11-09

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policies for Great Lakes Higher Education Corporation and Affiliates

## Personal Information Policies

  * Great Lakes Higher Education Guaranty Corporation
  * Northstar Guarantee Inc.
  * Northwest Education Loan Association
  * United Student Aid Funds

## Online Privacy Practices

  * Great Lakes Higher Education Guaranty Corporation
 
  * Northwest Education Loan Association
  * United Student Aids Funds

If you have any questions, please contact us at [privacy@glhec.org](mailto:privacy@glhec.org).

## Other Privacy Policies

  * Great Lakes Educational Loan Services, Inc.
  * U.S. Department of Education

## Website Privacy Policy

### Our Privacy Commitment

Your privacy is important to us. Great Lakes has a strong commitment to providing excellent service, including respecting concerns about privacy. Below are the guidelines we use for protecting the information you give us or we obtain when you use this website.

### Information We Collect When You Visit this Site 

This website does not collect personally identifiable information from your computer when you browse this site. This means that unless you provide us with personally identifiable information, voluntarily and knowingly, we will not know your name, your email address, or any other personally identifiable information about you.

We do automatically collect and store: the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the browser software you use and your operating system; the date and time you access our sites; and, the Internet address of the site from which you linked directly to our site. We track this information for all users, including those with "Do Not Track" signals enabled in their web browsers. We use this information to evaluate use of the site, to address any problems or issues with the site, and to help us make our site more useful. Great Lakes will not sell or give this information to a third party for purposes unrelated to Great Lakes, except that Great Lakes may disclose this information as it considers necessary to comply with a legal requirement, and in connection with investigating fraudulent activity or the misuse of this site. 

### Cookies

Our website uses "cookie" technology to offer a more convenient user experience. "Cookies" are strings of text that a website stores on a user's computer. A cookie enables the website to keep track of a user's activity and preferences within the website. Great Lakes does not share the information contained in cookies with unrelated third parties and does not allow unrelated third parties to set cookies on user computers. This means other parties cannot collect your personally identifiable information when you use our website.

### The Information We Collect When You Request a Service

When you request a service that is offered on this website, we collect information from you to provide you that service. You will be required to provide some information and other information that is requested may be provided at your option. All personal information we collect from you is covered by the Great Lakes Privacy Policy for Customer Information whether or not you were required to provide it. Unrelated third parties are not permitted to collect personally identifiable information about your online activities when you use our website.

### Information Sharing

The information that you provide us in connection with a service you request is not shared with anyone else except as necessary to provide the service and as permitted by law. The information we collect depends on the type of service you request.

### Links

This site provides links to resources that we think you might find useful. These sites operate under different, unique privacy policies. You must review the various privacy policies at linked sites. We have no control over the information that you might submit to them.

### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

Great Lakes does not intend to obtain information from children under 13 years of age. If we learn that we have collected information from a child under 13, we will promptly take all reasonable steps to delete the information. If a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, a parent or guardian may contact us and we will remove the information.

### Correcting Your Information

If you find what you believe is an error or inaccuracy in your records, please contact us as soon as possible. Great Lakes will investigate and correct any inaccurate or incomplete information as quickly as possible.

### Our Commitment to Data Security

We take strict security precautions to protect your confidential information. We permit only authorized employees who are trained in the proper handling of customer information to have access to confidential customer information. View more information about how we keep your information safe.

### Privacy Statement Changes

In the future, we may need to change our privacy statement. All changes will be made here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we use that information, and in what form and under what circumstances we will disclose it to another party. This policy is effective when it's posted on this website and will be reviewed from time to time. 

* * *
